Hello, Aries. Thank you so much for
being members. This is going to be a
week. All right. And I'm not I'm just
going to say it. I called it. I called
it. I knew this was going to be a big
week for you, but look at what happens.
Like look at all this opportunity and
this new thing and it just brings you
back into this like ah I feel
refreshed. But like Aries 2.0 Oh, now
this week, by the way, it so when I was
looking at this week, I was like, it
really does feel like the beginning of a
month, it just feels like there's this
ending beginning. It just So, what we're
going to do is like what we do for the
monthly forecast. I'm going to, you
know, we're going to look at a couple,
you know, areas of your life and pull
some cards. Okay. I feel like that felt
and that's why I did the just I just
felt like this was more important.
And again, you do see like you see the
it's a big thing. Yeah. All right. So,
uh are you also by the way are you
holding on to were you let go of um were
you let go of a job or you know maybe
you're you know they cut back or that's
coming through
but again it was the best thing for you.
That's the thing. It's like if you see
that, if you hold on to that energy like
I was let go down in the dumps and
you're in that low frequency energy,
it's going to be harder. It make you're
just hard on yourself. But you got to
see it as like that was meant to be,
right? So when you vibrate at that
higher frequency, when you are that
magnet attract and it doesn't have to,
it can be anything. It could be loving
it. It could be what whatever you want.
Like people that's when people notice
you, you know, they see your light. All
right, let's see what's going on for
love. Actually, let's do love and
relationships first with all this like
sneaky little partnership stuff that
keeps coming up.
Okay, love and relationships for Aries.
I need my um
Okay. Yeah. Two of Pentacles. It just
seems like there's going to be a little
bit of like let's
let's just do what you need to do during
the retrograde. Okay,
go within. All right.
Uh are y'all Some of y'all may be
between two. You know what I mean? All
right. So, just with love and
relationships, but some of y'all just
may be on the fence about something.
Some of y'all just may not know. There's
this kind of like, you know, and not in
a bad way. It's just like because here's
the thing. Even if you're here watching
for your sun sign, right? I've explained
this. Sometimes it's not about you like
the aspects that are happening. It's
about the people in your life that are
important or the circumstances. So, it
does feel like there may just be a point
this week you're at this juncture like
okay and what can we do together that
you know will bring that balance and
harmony into you know our relationship
that makes it feel fun and good. I mean
you've got Mercury and Leo. You're going
to have the sun in Leo very soon. So,
I'll even clarify that. But there does
feel like
let's bring some I'm going to show you
something here. Okay. Look at your
entire spread. Yeah.
You only got one card that's cups. Okay.
And it's the one where he's leaving
them. So, heart-based living this. Okay.
Really connect with the heart this week.
All right. Just letting you know that
it's a lot of wands. Like you're I told
you you're going to feel something
inside you like like really spirited.
Um okay.
You only got one swords too, right?
Yeah. That's fine. All right. I want to
clarify that two of pentacles.
So if if you are new when you get the
same card from two different uh decks,
you really want to pay attention. Okay.
There's something here. There's
something here with the you got the T of
swords twice and we're talking about
love and relationships. So again, the
biggest thing that's coming up for me is
there's something that you have to it's
the way that you're seeing something.
And the thing is like there may have
been an ending. There may have been
something that may be ending this week.
And I'm not saying it is the actual
relationship. There could be something
that again something that's reached a
point of fatigue. We eat pizza, you
know, every Tuesday. Let's shake it up
and eat tacos. Whatever it is, there's
got to be some new life into something
here. Okay. But there is something here
where yeah, this week you could feel a
little bit like a there's something just
not working. Not working. And it could
be you and the way that you're seeing
something and should something happen to
you in a relationship where you know
there are some conversations and you're
just like, "Oh, I that came out of
nowhere, right?" and I feel a little bit
betrayed and a little you know then
that's when you have to okay ask
yourself what was I meant to learn from
not that conversation but the
conversation not the words that were
said but why did that happen that
circumstance yeah so I know we're going
deep we're going deep but you do have
the north node in your 12th so you're a
fine I'll clarify that for you too okay
10 of sword uh Yeah, have your moment.
It really is all about going within. You
have the three of cups. Okay, so that's
a card of celebration and again three
vibration of the Empress. Okay, do
something new. Shake things up. All
right. Now, um career. And if you're not
here for career, let's just we're
calling it career, purpose, or passion.
And it's a it's a big week for that.
Yeah. Knight of Swords. Yeah. Okay. Um
there's again a little bit of like
the knight of the knight of swords can
be a little impulsive
but the great thing is so just be
mindful of that like just because you're
going to feel so fired up and you have
all these retrogrades asking you to just
let's so here's the thing with this
knight of swords coming up for career.
Go for it. Go for it. Let your mind
roam. Think outside the box, break, have
those breakthroughs, break free, all of
that. All right. You're going to feel
very stimulated and there may be
something that you see that you're just
like, "Okay,
next level.
Go after it. Go after it." Okay. But
remember, not the best week to like
have important conversations or but if
it's people from the past, yeah, that
could be great. In fact, Knight of
Swords is a Gemini card. Okay. Knight of
swords is Gemini and so there can be
something here with conversations, big
important conversations that you may
have but it just feels more of this
stimulation. Just don't be over,
you know, forceful because he can be a
little bit but this is great. Okay, just
again a lot of stimulation when it comes
to career or purpose or passion. You're
going to have a lot of ideas that you
want to run with now but take time to
map it out. Health. Let's see what's
going on with health.
All right.
Yeah. Okay. Uh, it seems like you're
really good here, but you've got to let
that thing go. All right. I say that
because you got the Ace of Wands. And
when we talk about health, remember, you
have Mars conjuncting the South Node in
Virgo in your sixth house of health. So,
something's got to go. Once it's gone,
you let in the new. Okay. You got the
Ace of Wands and the Page of Wands. All
right. out amazing. So there's this new
chapter for you. There's this, you know,
um that again a lot of sexual energy to
be honest and that could be the thing
that you know whatever it is it's
everything's connected. Physical health,
mental health, emotional health, you
know, once you got to do your thing, but
there is uh you know it's a good time.
It looks really good. But you remember
out with the old let's just get let's
make room for the Ace of Wands. Okay.
And once again, just very spirited, lot
of like vitality there. I mean, it's
just really nice. Okay. And remember,
Mars and Virgo anyway, you're going to
be feeling very physically driven and
you want to dance and do things.
Amazing. Health looks good. Biggest
message for Aries. What is your biggest
message this week?
The pay special attention to card.
For Aries, it would be um
that uh
stay focused. You're on your way. You're
going to get everything you want. You
have the 10 of pentacles.
It's the like highest of the highest of
the pits.
You're I mean this card is legacy. Yeah.
And remember, you have a lot of home,
family, significant other. All that
energy is just so activated. And then
remember, you're moving. You've you a
lot of you are literally but you you
you've got that conjunction the Venus
Jupiter conjunction to look forward to
in August just right after that new
moon. There's a lot happening for you.
There's a lot happening for you. Okay.
So, I love this. This is like the you
made it card. So, that's your big
message. You're on your way and stay
focused on your future. This is your
future. Yeah, you're good. You're
actually really good. It's just that.
Let's just All right, Aries, y'all are
amazing. Thanks. so much. I will see you
next week. Bye-bye. Hi Taurus. Thank you
so much for being members. I am so
excited for you. I cannot believe like
this is insane. So what I'm going to do
this week is because when I was looking
at this week, it is one of those weeks
where it just kind of like sneaks up on
you, right? Um because it's, you know, a
few aspects that are happening, but of
course I'm, you know, look at the
asteroids and and and everything else
and I'm just like a little bit more to
this story. And then I take a like I
kind of zoom out a bit. I'm like this is
actually possibly,
you know, between the full moon and the
new moon possibly the most important
week of the month. So um what I'm going
to do is because it does feel like this
like
renewal, this new energy that's coming
through, death to the old, old, out with
the old, in with the new, I'm going to
do uh what I do with a monthly forecast
cuz it it just feels strong. Okay. So,
let's let's look at a couple themes
here. We'll pull some cards. All right.
So, let's start with um love
love and relationships for Taurus. You
can expect Okay, you got the knight of
swords. So, there may be something here
with relationships you got to think
about. And I'm not surprised because
again, I was just just the fact that you
have all this 12th house activity. I
just remember the other thing with the
south node in Virgo that's the thing
some of you are going to have
there may be some endings here you know
but it wouldn't be it it just feels like
there yeah with Juno in the mix there
may be some like endings like
relationships it seems very mutual but
you know it maybe also if you had for
instance like
friends with benefit situation
And this week you realize like I want to
fall in love. I want to really you know
I want to have a family like things like
that. Like that's what you're letting go
with the Mars South node conjunction.
But whatever it is don't over analyze
things. Don't over just go with your
higher mind, right? That's all you have
to do. All right. So that's the nine of
swords. So with love and relationships,
yeah, there could be something on your
mind, but it just feels like there's
it's not you. It's like someone is
making you feel a certain way. All
right. So remember, Mercury retrogrades,
perfect time to have conversations to,
you know what I mean? Like I said, I
feel like y'all are making up with, you
know, there may be something I I'll
clarify that one for you. So, uh, you've
got the, uh, and remember, when you have
the same, if you're new, if you have the
same card come through from two
different decks, it's you really have to
pay attention. The universe really wants
you to pay attention to this. Okay, you
got the nine of pentacles
twice. Twice. It's in the heart of your
spread. Okay, twice.
So
that's two nines. You know what nine is?
It's like endings anyway, right?
Preparing for the new. And you you went
from nine of swords to nine of
pentacles. And the nine of pentacles is
more you anyway, right? It being a
earthbound. So that looks really good.
And remember, she's free to herself. So
whatever's happening here, just free
herself. It can be, it doesn't have to
be the exact relationship. It could be
something that you're thinking about,
okay? Where you're like, if there's
something that you're just like have the
conversations you need to have, free
yourself in any way that you can.
And all that wealth, all that wealth
that waits for you. Okay, so let's see.
Um, let's look at career. That's a big
Let's look at career. And if you're not
working, let's call it career,
passion, purpose. Okay. Career, passion,
purpose.
By the way, um Oh, hold on. Let me say
something.
Okay.
Ah, seven of wands. Yeah. You worked
hard to get where you're at. You're not
going to let that the seven of wands is
all about valor. It's all about standing
your ground. It's all about like Yeah.
That don't know. I just went through,
you know, seven years of Uranus in my
sign. You're trying to No, you don't.
So, this is that confidence I was
talking about knowing your worth, not
letting anyone take anything away from
you that you worked hard for. Okay?
because that may it may be a thing where
people want what you have because you're
really r literally rising above six of
wands seven of wands um what I was going
to say is that that nine of pentacles um
it's a good indicator of and this is for
love and relationships too but uh or
that's what it was pulled for but
remember it was in the heart of your
spread it's a good indicator of like
retirement too okay so uh health
for Taurus sun, moon, and rising. You're
you're you're going to be the rock for
people. You got the emperor. You're
going to be uh like owning who you are.
This is mastery of self. You're good.
You're I mean, he is the ruler of the
land.
He calls the shot. So again with a lot
of fourth house activity and then Saturn
Neptune in your 12th I just feel like
remember what I said earlier that
spiritual leader that you know uh role
model the hero energy like yeah oh yeah
do you see why people are looking up at
you like yeah now the last one the
biggest message for t uh Taurus for
tarot
what is the biggest message what should
Taurus really pay attention into this
month.
Seven of cups.
Know what you want. That's all it is.
Know what you want. You do have a lot of
12th house activity and with the north
node in Pisces which rules the 12th
house. And then you know that Virgo
Pisces access is uh interesting this
week. But just know what you want.
You're going to be fine. That's the
seven of cups. All right. Um, and it
looks like you might want different
things, but that's why I'm saying uh
have the merging of the physical mind
and the higher mind. Okay, I'll I'll
clarify that seven of cups with. But
that's just really just saying like
when you map out your future, make sure
that it's you being your authentic self.
It's no one else like yeah,
four of pentacles. So that's another
thing pay attention to like a big
message for you. You're working on the
foundations of your life
like for real for the next few years
building that strong foundation. So
just focus on that too. Okay. And that's
actually really great. I'm glad that the
four of pentacles came out because that
brings a lot of grounded energy. It's
like being very real like realistic,
very practical. It's Yeah. So really
nice. I'm going to clarify the four of
pentacles too. Um, the other reason why
I think it's interesting the four of
pentacles came out is because you did
come after that full moon in Capricorn
last week. So, a lot of it may just be
on your mind anyway. So, it's just
saying like continue to do that. Yeah.
And you have the eight of cups. Okay.
You got to leave something. You know
that. And it just seems like you are
going to Okay. It seems like you are
going to, but a lot of it is when you
have that practicality, when you're like
centered and grounded. Yeah. Eight of
eight of cups. You're like, "Okay, I got
to leave this in the past during the
week of the Mars South conjunction."
Yeah. And that's great because that's
passion. That's power. It's like you
recognizing, remember what I said, it's
all about self worth, self value. You're
recognizing something's better for you.
Amazing. Taurus, you're amazing. All
right. Thanks so much. I will see you
next week. All right. Bye-bye.
Hello, Gemini. Thank you so much for
being members. I'm gonna put my glasses
on. Um,
so
okay, here's the thing. If you are new,
one thing that I do sometimes, yeah, I
go directly into these second spreads,
but sometimes I just take a quick glance
and I get curious. I get curious. So,
let's see. Okay, let's clarify that
tower card. Yep.
What is it?
What the fax machine?
I can't.
You're good. That was meant for you.
That was meant for you.
You're free. You're free. That Knight of
Cups, you're free to explore. You got to
He's so romantic. He's just oh going out
there. Very dreamy energy, dreamer
energy. You got the north node in Pisces
trying them. You got He's Pisces by the
way. So much creative energy that I told
you about. Yeah, he's got the wings of
imagination on his helmet and his shoes.
So little bit of Mercury here too.
Remember you got Mercury and Leo in your
third. Anyway, do you remember last week
when I did this in the bonus spread too
for I forget what it was, but I I was
curious about something in your spread.
You got that the Knight of Cups. So,
there is something here with
partnerships, relationships. Um, there's
something here about you pursuing
something that's going to emotionally
fulfill you. And you see that here with
that King of Cups. That's where you want
to be.
Okay.
Best thing for you. All right. So
because of this week because it for me
it just feels like the death and rebirth
of something for every sign. There's
something un there's just something rare
that's happening this week. The way the
asteroid everything between the full
moon from last week and the new moon
next week. I just feel this is a really
strong week. Let's see what's going on
for So I'm going to do what I'm doing is
I'm pulling cards for just kind of how I
do the monthly forecast. Yeah. All
right. So let's uh let's do love first.
I'm going to see love, love and
relationships
for Gemini sun, moon, and rising. So,
uh, yeah, there you go. There's
something here that you've got to that
might be it
or that 10 of wands. That might be it.
Just to FYI.
And 10 of Wands is a third deck and a
Sagittarius. Sagittarius card.
Sagittarius rules your seventh house of
partnerships and relationships. And
Queen of Swords is Libra, by the way.
And Libra is the ruler of the seventh
house of partnerships and relationships
out. There may be something here that's
got to end. Okay? And again, it doesn't
have to be the relationship when it
comes to love and relationships. It
could be a way that maybe you are it's
something that you want and you're just
working so much. But ask yourself, am I
doing this
like for a reason? Yeah. Do I have to
recognize that's the thing that's got to
go? Is me sabotaging myself when it
comes to love and relationships? There's
something there where, you know, I want
it, but I'm not taking action for it.
I'm just going to work a lot and that's
my excuse. Do you know what I mean? So,
just keep that in mind. And again, every
all of y'all are different. You're going
to but at the end of the day that's the
10 of wands. You drop a wand or two. You
can see a little clearly. So you see
that like with that coming up the tower
here it just feels like there is you
have all this like free fun social
magnetic all of that but there is
something that's just like has to go and
are you recognizing it? Yeah. So I'll
clarify that 10 of wands for you.
You got two of them.
So, yeah, I just address it.
Okay. Any bottlenecks or anything that
feels
heavy
that'll lighten your load. You got the
King of Cups. If you're new, when you
get the same card from two different
decks, you got to really pay attention.
You really want that emotional
stability. And we're talking about cups,
which is love and relationships. You
won't be sitting in that throne. All
right. With your boo, two of wands.
Okay. So, again, another card that's
just saying, hey,
plan things out, map things out, look at
your future. How does this fit? Yeah.
How are you going to make room?
Or however you want to do what you want
to do with that magician that keeps
sticking to my elbow. Let's see what's
going on for um career purpose or
passion
because if you're not working Yeah.
won't focus on your like as if if you're
retired or whatnot. So career purpose or
passion.
There it is. I want to see this card
too. All right. So
let's see. Uh you have the six of
pentacles. Very nice. Very good. Very
good when it comes to career. That looks
great. And
you got the sun. Very good. Very
amazing. You're good. I tell you, your
career is like bonkers. Okay. Six of
pentacles. That's just amazing. That's,
you know, if you're seeking support,
it's coming. You've got support all
around you. There's this sense of like,
you know what I talked about like cause
and effect. There's a sense of like
taking that inspired action. You'll see
how much that changes your world. All
right? And you really feel that with
that six of pentacles. And so yeah,
that's wealth. But wealth comes in so
many different forms. Okay. And then you
have the sun. What did I talk about? The
queen of wands in the heart of your
spread. The sun being the biggest yes in
tarot, by the way. So things look really
good. You have that full abundance. The
sun. It feels like there's some It feels
like there's something here that's just
like setting you up to have a lot of
power, but like have fun with it, too.
Remember, the sun is optimism. It's
vitality. It's opportunities.
It's a cleansing. It's a lot. It's your
good. Now, let's look at health.
All right, Gemini.
King of Wands. Um, you're getting all
these leaders. You got the King of Cups,
Queen of Cups. Um, yeah. So, uh, the
King of Wands, I mean, you got the King
and the Queen. So, the King of Wands
when it comes to health, just you're
going to feel very spirited.
That raises your frequency. That King of
Wands, so much fiery energy. And again,
this week, you're going to you're you're
busy. You're busy. You're social. You're
networking. And that's a King of Wands.
He is very social, too. And he is, you
know, the entrepreneur. He's the fun
king as well. So it's when you have that
joy in your life, all that passion in
your life that affects all like mental
health, emotional health, physical
health, all of it. Okay. So have that
passion, feel that passion.
Do not deny yourself of that passion.
Now, uh
what is the biggest message for Gemini?
All right.
I kind was trying to guess. Um, I got
close, but you got the knight of swords.
You got your card. So, the biggest
message, slow down.
There's going to be it seems like you're
going to be very social. You're it's a
Knight of Wands. But what's really great
about this, like I said, there's a lot
of confident boosting energy that's
happening in your sign this week. The
Knight of Swords. Remember what I said
about like fear being fiction. Like he's
fearless. He goes into the storm. He
gets what he wants. It's the sword. So,
it's a very cerebral. It's also like
communicative. It's getting what you
want through conversations.
You're the Geminis's anyway. You're good
at that, being persuasive,
all of that. So, there may be something
here that yeah, your biggest message is
being the messenger with that knight of
swords. You could be delivering a
message, but there's a lot going on
through your mind. But that's why I'm
saying slow down because he can go a
little fast. He can be a little
impulsive.
And normally I would be like go go go
forth, go with the wind. But with all
these retrogrades that are asking you
to, you know, try not to like,
okay, because you're going to see that
with your mind's going really fast and
you want to take action, you want to do
this, you want to do this, when all the
energy is trying to just pull you back a
little bit, just a little bit, okay? You
can still do things, but just make sure
that you still take action. That's the
biggest message, okay? Just continue to
take action. Just try not to be like
very impulsive. You got that Knight of
Cups. I mean, Knights are all about
action, by the way. They have a drive
and purpose. And so, you're going to
feel very driven this week. You're going
to feel very driven. You're amazing.
Thanks so much, Gemini. I will see you
next week. All right. Bye-bye. Hello,
Cancer. Thank you so much for being
members. Um, listen, this is going to be
a week.
It's a great week again. It just feels
like big. It feels big. It feels there's
like something major happening. But
again, Mars conjuncting uh the south
node is also going to be really big too
because there's going to be something
here.
Again,
sometimes there are things that you
don't want to let go, but Mars is going
to be like you got it. But Juno's in the
mix, too. So Juno's, you know, helping
you saying, "Okay, let's talk about
this. Maybe even compromise."
But yeah, I do have to recognize this is
I've learned my lesson. Okay. Um,
so what I'm doing, you hear the church
bells.
Okay. So, what I'm doing for you now is
I'm just going to do what I usually do
for the monthly forecast because there's
so much happening in terms of all this
new energy, but then all this retrograde
energy. So, I really wanted to see where
we're at now
with certain themes, okay, in your life.
So, we're going to start with love,
okay? Love and um
I'm going to look at those later. uh
love and relationships for cancer,
okay? Because you do have that new moon
coming up. Uh there's just so much other
stuff. Like I said, July is bonkers,
okay? Love and relationships. Oh, okay.
Eight of Pentacles. So, um biggest thing
that's coming through is patience.
Practice patience. There's a sense of
you working on something, okay? Or you
need to work on something, but take that
time for you. I feel like there's
something again when you're in touch
with your intuition and with Uranus in
your 12th house again very even healing
energy. Don't forget Chiron's in the mix
too. But there we're talking about love
and relationships. You have the eight of
pentacles. It's building towards
something. Okay? Working together,
building towards something, okay? Even
if you're single, building towards
something. Even if you have to like put
out a PowerPoint, you know, deck for
yourself. Again, I'm not even joking.
with all these planets retrograde and
you got Mars and Virgo which again very
detail oriented very like perfectionist
energy but that's other thing with Mars
in the south end Virgo try not to be
overcritical overly perfectionist energy
that can happen and it could be the way
that you're communicating with people as
well it is your third house all right
let's take a look at these cards there
was a bunch that fell out for you know
love when the when the church bells
Okay. King of uh pentacles
with that eight of pentacles. Four of
swords. Mhm.
Stillness of mind. Yeah. Temperance.
Pretty much the same thing. You have a
lot here saying patience,
patience. That's it. That's your biggest
takeaway. Okay. Have that patience.
Stay grounded. Well, there's pentacle
energy and then temperance, which is
enjoy the moment, okay? Don't get all
swept up in here. Remember, that's going
to be for some of y'all. Yeah, just have
that patience. It is a time with the
prison portal as well as for retrogrades
and Mercury going retrograde. All right.
Now, um
that's so that's your big message. Now,
let's take a look at your career. Okay.
Let's say career, purpose, passion. Yep.
If you're retired or not working,
career, purpose, passion for cancer.
All right. Ah, you and all your
pentacles. 10 of pentacles again, career
is the biggest highlight. You have
Saturn and Neptune there. Okay. In your
10th, you're really figuring out like
what's real for me. I would you know uh
if anything was like fantasy right with
Neptune retrograde anything that was
fantasy it's like let's we got to pull
ourselves out of that but that's great
10 of pentacles for career there's there
is that finish line it looks really good
okay 10 of pentacles is legacy it's a
you made it card and remember the ride
await smith deck it's like the pentacles
raining from the heavens and this card
is actually attributed to Mars and Virgo
can you believe that and then you have
Mars and Virgo comes into the South
node. So once again when I just see
what's happening for you that just seems
like there's a big change. All right.
Now let's see in a good way with that
and not only astrologically but with
that T of pentacles. Now let's see uh
health. Okay. Virgo does rule like
health,
mental health, emotional health,
physical health, social health,
spiritual health.
Is all right. Cancer sun, moon, and
rising. Oh,
there's a lot of cards that want to come
out. Okay, let's go that one and I'll
take a look at those.
Judgement. All right, so there is
definitely something here. You have to
wake up. I'm not saying you're not
awake.
A lot of the cards that came out is
like, and again, you have Uranus in your
12th. You have the North Node in your
9inth.
There is something here. You can't
forget about Pluto in your eighth. Yeah,
this card actually judgment is
attributed to Pluto. This is the wakeup
call, spiritual awakening. Some of
youall getting a second chance at
something too. Um, and that is going to
make the difference when you actually
have that breakthrough, when you see the
thing that you have to see, when you
make that change that you need to make.
Okay? So, just keep that in mind. All
right. I'm going to pull one from from
these that came out uh when it comes to
health because that when I say that
that's what fixes not fixes but like
improves mental health, emotional
health, physical they're all connected.
There's some some big thing that you've
got to see. Okay. It's got to come
within you. All right. I want to do this
one. Yeah. You got the high priestess.
So there's your affirmation. Go within.
Go within. But be in touch with your
intuition. There are some things that
you can't see, Cancer. But if you go
within,
oh, you can see, okay? When you when you
really dive in that intuitive energy,
okay, remember he's got his hands over
his face. These two are, you know,
chained to the devil. So, they're like,
and then you got the seven of cups. He
can't. It's all foggy.
You got to go within. All right. Now,
the pay special attention to card. What
should Cancer pay special attention to
this week.
Your biggest message would be
four of pentacles.
Look at that. Stability, structure,
working on the foundations of your life.
That's what Jupiter exalted in your sign
is anyway. So, keep doing you. And don't
forget the like fundamentals. Don't
forget even like who you are and the
world that you want to build for
yourself. Okay. Four of Pentacles is
also like don't let things get like just
be on top of everything. Be on top of
everything and don't let circumstances
own you, right? Remember there is a
sense of you becoming a lot more
confident this week. Use it. Okay. But a
lot of it here with all these swords
too. It's like it's going to help right
here. Let's move in this new direction.
Remember, all this is just potential,
too. So, if you move in that direction
of that high frequency, you're going to
be 1,000% fine. But there is that
potential like, okay, did I make the
right choice or someone did something to
me and now that got in my way. Why would
you let anyone take your power, right?
And that's you can be standing your
ground for that. But there's still
something here that's like, okay, let me
continue to work on these. Work on me
during these retrogrades
and I'll know and I'll have that moment
of clarity, that spiritual awakening
that I'm seeking. It's you're actually
really good to be honest. Just don't um
you just got to see something in a
different way. That's all it is. Okay?
And I truly believe you will with the
Uranus and your 12th. Cancer, y'all are
amazing. Happy birthday. I will see you.
And yeah, big things to come. You want
to see the Let's see. Yeah. Let's see
with the world. You got that eight of
swords. That's what it is. That's what
it is. You're moving into something new.
You could have already started planning
it. Now, these retrogrades is like
you're you're like doubting yourself and
you're you see that, right? Do not.
And that's what happens when we move
into new places in our life for new
directions, new job, new relationship.
There can be a little bit of that. Don't
don't do that. Yeah, you got the moon.
I'm going do one more. There's something
here that uh six of wands. That's really
great. Yeah. So,
I'm going to let me just do one more. We
got that four of swords again. So, do
you see what's happening here? Something
new. Something that even new that hasn't
even happened yet. something that you
want to do but there is a sense of like
with all these retrogrades you're going
within a lot of the past coming back
there can be something here where it's
part of that south node it's just like
because it's in your third again third
is the mind right so there's something
here it seems like it's a test for you
that's all it is you can see that
clearly there's something here testing
you and
you can pass you that six of wands you
got that four of swords things are
happening fastaster past for you. You're
going to be good. It's just it really is
saying the only thing that get in your
way would be yourself of here. Don't
over analyze. Don't overthink. Go with
the flow. Flow with the go. And know
that everything that's happening is
leading you toward everything that you
want. You got to you got to lead the way
though. All right. You got to be that
leader. Anyway, Cancer, you are those
you are that leader. Six of Wands really
great. That card actually is attributed
to Jupiter in in Leo. And so remember
Jupiter is actually moving into Leo next
year while we have the eclipses in in
Leo and Jupiter will trine Saturn and
Aries. That is just insane for you. I've
talked about this. You're moving into
this amazing period with Saturn in your
10th. You got um you know uh you're
going to have Jupiter and Leo in your
second.
That's salary, income, finances, and uh
career and fame. Like, you're moving it
like anyway, you're good. You know
you're good. Just don't overthink
things, okay? And let the things go that
you know you need to let go. All right.
Thanks so much, Cancer. I'll see you.
Happy birthday. Thank you. Byebye. See
you next week. All right. Thank you.
Hello, Leo. Thank you so much for being
members, y'all. I'm going to That was
bonk. Like, I can't even I can't um
wow. I just can't. It's like everything
that you want you're going to have. But
it really is that patience part. And I
do have to remind you and it's again I
was going to talk more about this next
week, but when the sun moves into your
sign with Mercury in your sign and there
are going to be a little you know some
aspects that are you know next week just
be mindful of remember the lure
expression of you know some aspects
happening in your sign as Leo can be
like pride and ego. Okay. So, just bear
that in mind because there's a lot with
Mercury retrograde in Leo. Yeah, there's
a lot of like my way, nope, my way.
Nope, my way. With other people and
you're going to be so social. All right,
keep that in mind. But, um, this is
amazing. Um, you're good. You're
absolutely good. I can't even like
I just did not expect that. Like, you're
really really really good. Okay. So,
Leo, what I'm going to do is that um
I wanted to do just because where we are
right now, like mid July, after
everything that we went through the
first two weeks of July and what you're
about to experience this week and then
next week, it really does feel like this
is a strong week. So, I'm going to treat
this like a monthly forecast. I'm going
to pull cards for love, career, health,
all of that. Like your biggest message.
So, let's break it down. Okay. So, let's
look at love and relationships first.
Okay.
Leo sun, moon, and rising because it
feels like a reset to be honest. Um, you
got another three three of pentacles.
Uh, that's really great. So, remember I
said love and relationships. There's
remember pentacles are your physical
reality, your physical realm. This card
really is about all about working with
others, teamwork. Let's see eye to eye.
Let's build this together. Okay. And
that is where you really feel that like
spirit of consciousness.
This is actually
really amazing. Okay.
really good because it looks like there
is either something that you're it feels
a lot for a lot of y'all like rebuilding
or want to rebuild or want to move in a
different direction or you're just
entering a new part like something new.
Remember this is creation. Yeah, the
Empress you got death change. Okay. And
so there's something here new that's
happening in your life when it comes to
love relationships. It could be the way
that you're seeing, you know, current
relationships, how you've perceived
relationships,
changing the way that you see
relationships with Uranus and Gemini
with Mercury retrograde in your sign.
Okay? Or working or you know building
something with someone from the past.
Now let's see career. Okay. And let's
say career, purpose or passion or and
yeah, if you're not working, if you're
retired, career, purpose, passion,
Leo, uh, five of pentacles.
So there you go. Do you see how that
explains a lot here? Yeah, there's, like
I said, a lot of y'all are changing jobs
or it's already happened. That's the
other thing. If there was a circumstance
where you didn't see it coming or you
know what I mean like maybe your team
was laid off or you you know maybe a
client left or whatever don't
hold on to that energy it had nothing to
do with you. Yeah. Don't create this
whole Yeah. That's that five of
pentacles. That's what it's saying.
You're moving into new things anyway. I
gave you like five reasons why you have
a lot to look forward to. Okay. So this
is a little bit of like um yeah there's
something that's happening uh career
purpose passion where you may feel like
some there's a slowdown or something's
holding you back or there's something
here where it's
there could have been a circumstance
that put you in place of like
but remember the five of pentacles it's
all about there's this sanctuary all
around you all you have to do is reach
out okay these people are outside the
church then they refuse to go in. So
there's this element of focusing on
their plight and their woes rather than
like taking charge doing something like
get changing your life right so just
keep that in mind okay so should
something happen remember there's
something amazing on the other side you
have death with the empress there's
something absolutely amazing okay um so
a lot of y'all want to make changes
anyway so just don't doubt yourself
either okay I'll yeah I'll clarify
Uh yeah, there you go. You got the
devil.
You got to let it go. There's something
here. You got to make sure that you see
what it is. You got the moon in your
crown. The devil. So, a lot of this is
subconscious energy. What is the
subconscious is where we store our
memories.
What is that? Past. What is happening
this week? You got four planets
retrograde. You got Mercury retrograde
in your sign. The past. Okay. So,
there's something that you're chained to
that's making you think a certain way
when something happens or even in a
situation that could happen this week.
No, that would be that devil energy,
that trickery energy. Yeah, they're
taking your energy.
So, you got to break free from the
chains, whatever it is, and then you're
set free. Remember, you got a lot to
look forward to. Okay? And I'm going to
show you something here, by the way.
It's the same people, the same thing.
It's the same thing. Okay, you see that,
right? Knight of Cups and uh the Death
card. So, it's almost like you're
manifesting something that you want, but
you can't doubt yourself. That that's
where it gets a little just don't doubt
yourself. Remember, I said this is a
week where you're focusing on
confidence. You have Mars conjunct the
south node in your second house of self
worth and self value. If you don't see
yourself, you know, in a place where,
you know, I deserve a raise or I deserve
this or this is, you know what I mean?
Like then, yeah, that that would keep
you in that low energy frequency. So,
just ask that's why you have to go
within. You got to figure out what it is
to let it go and release it. Okay? Now,
and pay attention to your dreams. Now,
the third thing is uh health. Let's look
at health.
All right, Leo. H you got the world. I'm
getting a little bit of uh world on your
shoulder energy. Yeah, there's something
ending the world, right? Being the end
of the uh major. Yeah. Uh arcana, the
fool's journey. Do you remember your
reading from last week? You got the
magician and the fool. So you got like
this new. So anyway, it just feels like
there's it's a patience thing as well.
Practice patience. You see everything's
about to change for you. Don't doubt
yourself. Uh be able to, you know, see
the changes happening in your life. Um
and enjoy it. Enjoy life. I mean this is
amazing but at the same time it does
feel a little bit of like there could be
this disconnect
mind body spirit all together put it all
together and I'm just saying that here
with with how this is laid out but I
love that it's just again showing that
once you take that burden off yourself
and remember we're talking about health
that improves mental health physical
health emotional health all of it
spiritual health so be proud of
yourself. Okay, be proud of yourself.
You made it to the end. You got this
amazing new and even if you don't know
what it's like and that makes you a
little you're good. You got all this
abundance leadership all of that. You're
good. All right. Now, the biggest
message for Leo would be
this would be the pay special attention
to card. What should Leo pay? Yeah.
Uh, I don't know why I did that, but if
you're new, when you get the same card
from two different decks, that's over
170 cards, you know, the universe is
trying to tell you something, especially
for the pay special attention to card.
The biggest message,
three of wands. Okay, so pay special
attention to this. Two things. one.
Yeah, there's something here where it's
like you've got to get out of um
it's like an ambivalence. Okay. Also
being hard on yourself. These they're
ready to go. They're ready to go, but
you got to know when that green light is
lit for you. Okay. Remember Mercury's
retrograde and it doesn't mean you can't
start new things but at least take the
time this week with Mars conjunct Virgo
because that will clear a lot of energy.
March conjunct the south node in Virgo
that'll clear a lot of energy and bring
a lot more clarity. Yeah. And it's it's
it's it's a lot of weight off your
shoulder. All right. whatever you
release. But if there's anything, you
are getting a green light. This is
indicating you're about to embark on
this brand new journey, this brand new
era.
Be prepared, though. And to be prepared,
you got to have that. You have to go
within. Okay, Leos, y'all are amazing. I
will see you next week. All right.
Bye-bye. Hello, Virgo. Thank you so much
for being members. Um, listen. So, what
I'm doing for you this week is that I'm
not doing a spread, but because this
week feels so much like a death and
rebirth, right, for every sign with Mars
on the south node, with all these
retrogrades, with people thinking about
the new new them, with the prism portal.
Um, what I'm going to do is what I
usually do for the monthly forecast. I
want to do a check-in. Okay? So, we're
going to look at a couple themes. Okay?
We're going to pull some cards here. And
the first we're going to start with is
love and relationship. So, what can
Virgo expect this week? Yeah, love and
relationships.
What was it?
And if you're new, by the way,
um when you get the same card from two
different decks, that's over 160 cards.
You know that the universe is telling
you something here and you really want
to pay attention. So when it comes to
love and relationships, you got the King
of Pentacles twice. Okay. Now, here's
the thing, Virgo. Yeah, this is a big
focus on being that, you know, in a
relationship. You want to be there. You
want to be present. You want to show up.
You even want to show up for yourself to
show up. Okay. But there is a sense of
like feeling that comfort, feeling that
wealth in relationships where it's like,
I'm good. I'm good. I feel free as well.
This feels really good. and you've built
something here that you can be very
proud of or you're in the process of
building something, right? This is
saying go do it. Go build. If you're
single, go do it. Go build that. If
you're in a relationship where you're
like, what you got to do to feel
protected? Yeah. What do you have to do?
Okay. Where you also want to be that
person that is a provider too. It's all
about, you know, sharing the wealth. All
right? So, keep that in mind. But at the
end of the day, there is something here
where it's like this is wealth. His his
robe is integrated with the harvest.
Like you can't get more wealth. So it's
like yeah, that's your message. It's
like build that wealth or preserve that
wealth, but be you. Be your authentic
self and you're going to be fine.
Remember Taurus, okay? Your ninth house
wisdom, inner wisdom, how you see
things. Okay, this is really wonderful.
Okay. And by the way, I forgot to say
this in your main spread. You got the
only two people in all of tarot that
hold that golden scepter of abundance.
Anything they touch turns to gold.
You're good. You're really, really good.
All right. It's almost like the things
that you like really want, as long as
you put that energy there, oh yeah,
you're going to be rewarded. That's
that's the Empress. You You're being
rewarded. All right. Now let's take a
look at uh career. All right. And I'm
going to say career purpose or passion
as well. Okay. And passion because you
know if you're not working it would be
you know. Yeah. So anyway all in the
realm of career purpose or passion for
Virgo sun, moon and rising.
Okay let's see. Ah
I you got the three of pentacles. So for
career. Yeah, it does look like there is
something new with other people
involved.
Okay, maybe you're starting a new job,
maybe you're joining a new team, maybe
you are, you know, again, that's just
natural here. You know, you rule the
workforce, colleagues, employees. That's
a Virgo. Yeah. So, um, but yeah, again,
this week feels like this big a big
change that's happening, but that's
really great. There's something new that
you can look forward to. take that
action. You can make it happen. You see
what you're you see you're going to be
rewarded. You got a lot to celebrate
with that. Your life is changing. You
want it anyway. All right. And there's
structure with that with the three of
pentacles. Okay. Really wonderful for
the long term. Um but just remember it's
all about teamwork. So there's something
here with other people involved now. Um
but it is a three. What did I say? Birth
of new things but also wanting to learn,
grow, advance, develop, all of that.
Now, uh, health. Let's take a look at
health for Virgo sun, moon, and rising.
That's it. Okay.
Uh, health.
It's so funny because this card came up
to my uh or in my mind um when I was
shuffling um the but for your main
spread, I was like, I think they're
going to get and you got it. The eight
of wands. I was just like, there's
something here when you've got Mars on
the south node in your sign. There's
just something here. Remember, Mars is a
lot of energy. So that's amazing. You
know, the eight of wands. So, um, very
excited for you, very happy for you when
it comes to health. There's something
here that, you know, again, there may be
something here that there's movement
around or it could be you like being
very physically active, which is good
for your health. And remember,
everything's connected. When you're good
to your physical health, that's good for
your emotional health, for your mental
health, everything's connected, okay?
When it comes to health. All right? So,
one thing improves the other. This is
one. So, a lot just very free, very
invigorating. There's so much
enthusiasm, excitement. So, a lot of it
has to come with like the changes that
you're going through. All right. So,
really put energy into, you know, things
that are just just movement. It could
even be in the mind. Sure. Yeah. With
all this Mercury energy. Um, but, you
know, it it it it's whatever you want to
bring into your life because this is
everything aligning for you, right? But
you've remember you got to take that
action. I think this is the only wands.
Let me double check. The only wands that
you got. Okay. So feel it. Feel it. This
is great. Okay. We even call it, you
know, arrows of love. Okay. Wands of
love. So again, wherever you want to
direct that energy, whether it is
career, ones are also career. Yeah. At
the end of the day, it's your passions.
Where do you want to put that energy?
Things can happen fast when you put your
energy there. And then that improves
health. Now, last card. What is the
biggest message for Virgo sun, moon, and
rising? The pay special attention to
card.
All right. Your biggest message for this
week would be
good. You got the six of pentacles.
You got a lot of pentacles. So, money,
wealth. Like I said, you're really going
to feel that eighth house activity in a
big way.
I'm just saying. Juno, you're going to
feel really strongly this week. She is
in Scorpio in your second house of
money, too. income, salary, you're
signing things or thinking of signing
things or wanting something here that
but the six of pentacles, everything's
harmonizing for you. So, don't worry,
okay? You're going to be fine.
Everything's going to be great. You've
got to, you know, let something go.
Everything, especially in a financial
sense, but it's also like spiritual
wealth. It's that, you know, taking
those inspired actions is what brings
that spiritual wealth, right? Remember
that inspired actions like actions
literally in Sanskrit
translates to karma. So everything is
you being on this karmic journey. But
what I really love about this is the six
of pentacles even even in the
writerweight smith deck. Remember it's a
very philanthropic man with a scale in
his hand. What did I say about this 19
degree yeah conjunction that's happening
in your sign associated with Libra. So
balance, peace, harmony, all of that
based on your, you know, intentions,
inspired actions that you take. It's all
about connecting with others. Okay? All
about that because what comes after the
five of pentacles would be the six of
pentacles.
So don't be hard on yourself. There's
going to be you need support. It's right
there. It's coming. A lot of y'all, it's
going to be you. It's going to be you.
All right? and your sense of service to
others, supporting others, and that's
how your karma grows. Okay, so keep that
in mind because in the six of pentacles,
it is the young heropant.
You got the heropant. You're good,
Virgo. Y'all are amazing. Thank you so
much. I'm very excited for you and I'll
see you uh next week. All right. Thank
you. Bye-bye.
Hello, Libra. Thank you so much for
being members. Um you know what's really
funny? So the special different spread I
was going to do for you. It's not even a
spread. I'm going to pull some cards for
you. But because this week, and this is
just bonkers, the reason I'm doing this
is because this week does feel like a
big ending and a beginning, okay? There
just feels something big here and a big
transition too for a lot of y'all. And
so for a pretty much every sign. And so
what I'm going to do is like what I do
with a monthly forecast where I pull a
card well for some themes here. All
right? Because it really does feel this
like this reset. But then look at your
spread. You truly are going through one.
Yeah. You're truly going through a big
reset. A lot of big changes happening in
your life and you know it. Big changes
with with the death card, the tower, the
lovers. I can't even like look across
your cross. You got the Queen of Wands.
You got the Knight of Swords. You got
like
All right. Let's look at love and
relationships first because um that's
going to be on on your mind a lot of
y'all. Okay.
All right, Libra sun, moon, and rising.
What? Oh my gosh, I can't even. You got
temperance.
Amazing.
So, be very open to communicate.
Remember, you may have a tendency to
withdraw. Yeah, with that 12th house
activity, you also have that T of
swords. It's fine. You can do that. Have
meditative moments, but temperance is
all about like finding that inner
balance, moderation. You get this.
You're Libra, right? But the biggest
thing of all is practicing patience.
That's all. And I told you that there's
going to be a lot of y'all that are
going to be like, "Now I got to do this.
This has got to happen. This I need the
answer for this now." And like, "No, no,
no, no. You're going to be fine.
Everything's working out exactly the way
it's supposed to." All right. Remember,
we talked about divine timing. Now,
second, and this is love and
relationship. So, you're going to have a
lot of insights to when you like and
just enjoy the moment. That's all you
got to do. All right? Be present in the
moment. Now, second thing, uh, career.
And if you're not here for career, let's
call it career, purpose, or passion.
Okay. Okay. What do we have?
Queen of Swords. Queen of Swords is you.
You know that, right? And remember, I
said Juno is very active this week. And
she is again Jupiter's wife. All about
truth, justice. Aris is very active.
She's a little Yeah, Queen of Swords can
be that way. She's left all her emotions
at the door. She needs to. She doesn't
want her emotions to cloud her judgment.
Head above the clouds making big
decision. It seems like when it comes to
career, your purpose, um passion, there
is some sort of fairness that you're
seeking. There is something where you
are being your authentic self. Okay? You
want to let that side shine, but you
also want to like not let anyone push
you over, but also you don't want to be
like, you know,
to others.
It would be Mercury in Leo retrograde
too. It's like
let's look at health.
Let's look at health.
All right, Leo.
Leo, Libra.
So, if you are new, when you get the
same card from two different decks,
maybe you really want to pay attention.
The universe trying to tell you
something.
health. Okay, slow down. That's it. Slow
down. You got one card saying practice
patience. You got the queen of swords
who's very patient.
Two knight of swords. Slow down. That's
it. You can go after the things you
want, but don't get um you know,
people are may not be keeping up with
your pace.
Just remember, it's a weekly that's it.
It's is a weekly forecast. All right.
But the other thing is like don't also
um when it comes to health, it's more
about mental health here. Yeah, you've
got the Mars South node conjunction and
your 12th. All right. Up here, right? I
said all those planets, you know, in
that Mercury ruled sign that this is
happening in Knight of Swords is
Mercurial. He's Gemini. Yeah, that's in
your ninth. Your perspective on things.
So, there's something here where it's
just the bigger message coming through
for me. So he can be like a little in
like forceful, a little bit impulsive
too. And that is Uranian energy to be
honest. That impulsive like spontaneous.
So which is fine, but just make sure
that you're not like all over the place.
Yeah, use that because it is a lot of
fire and air honest like honestly this
week. So just stay a little bit grounded
and still say the things you need to
say, do the things you need to do.
That's fine. Just know that there may be
a little bit of like
we got to go a little bit slower just
for this week. Okay. Now, last thing is
uh the biggest message for Libra. What
does Libra need to know this month? I'm
sorry, this week. Yeah, this week. What
do they have to really pay attention to?
Some of y'all retiring.
Looks like it. Some of y'all are
thinking about retiring. Um, well, you
do have the nine of pentacles. You have
the nine of coins. Okay. So there is
something here where it's like your
biggest message is uh really working on
yourself. It does seem like there is
going to be something in terms of you
having your moment in terms of this is
the direction I'm going right all this
wealth not having to worry about money
not having to worry about anything being
in this you know garden of abundance
having worked my way hard. I've earned
my spot here. So that's really nice and
a lot of you are just going to get it.
You do you do you you do what you know
you're going to get it with that nine of
nine of pentacles which by the way is a
Virgo card and so what really comes
through strongly for me is like mind
over matter. Patience is a big thing by
the way but also like mind over matter
and that has to do with what's happening
for you anyway. Just any blockages up
here is
anything that you're doing, any habits,
any like like anything. Okay, it's it's
time to change things up. You're about
to move into
a lot of stuff next week. All right,
your life is changing. Libra, y'all are
amazing. And that's amazing. The nine of
pentacles, that's very auspicious. Okay.
A lot of like uh you know wisdom,
enlightenment and and again that
independence. It feels really good.
There's something here that you're going
to feel this wealth that feels really
good. Especially again with that three
of cups and that queen of wands, but
there is a little bit of like there's
something that's got to to get there.
Okay,
you're good. Libra, I'll see you next
week. Thank you so much. Bye-bye.
Hello, Scorpio. Thank you so much for
being members. Big week. All right. This
is, you know, again, I just to to be
honest, like there are some other signs
that have this Mars South node
conjunction. They'll feel it a little
bit. They're going to really feel it,
but for you, it just it just feels like
adjustments.
Uh but there is a little bit of
intensity with Uranus and Venus and your
eighth. But just keep that's with
relationships and you know, building
wealth. But you can clearly see you're
going to be fine. Just don't miss out on
that. Really going within to think about
your future. All right. Now, because
this week is one of those sneaky weeks
that is actually one of the most
important weeks, it's it's big.
Everything's connected. the eclipse that
we had the south node with Mars in Virgo
the eclipse that we're going to have in
Virgo in September everything it so it
does feel like this is like a death and
rebirth moment this week for every sign
so the spread it's not even a spread
that I'm going to do for you it's going
to be like the monthly forecast where
I'm going to pull some cards and we're
going to focus on different areas of
your life because it really does feel
like
there's some new chapter this week okay
so why don't we start with Um, love and
relationships. What can we expect for
Scorpio?
That card didn't well two cards didn't
want to go. All right. So, you have
you know what's really funny? I was
writing I was scripting everything out
for you know all the aspects that were
happening.
What's happening with a lot of the
asteroids of planettoids. It does feel
like there is a lot of queen energy and
you just got two queens. You got the
queen of wands and the which one? Queen
of pentacles, right? Yeah. Queen of
coins.
So amazing because one thing that I
didn't and that's the other thing if
you're new to this Whoa. I just
we we talk about some things here. Okay.
That maybe I didn't have time to. You
didn't get any wands. You got no wands.
Where's that passion? Where's that
passion? Ones are so invigorating. And
I'm not saying that it's like a bad
thing, good thing or anything like that.
It's just like, you know, there's no
want. So, you want to just consider
that. And uh there could just, you know,
you've got Mars and Virgo. It's a little
different, but it it blends well with
you being a water sign, Virgo being
earth. Use it. But anyway, Queen of
Wands. Remember I said you're going to
be a magnet this week. She's a magnet.
She gets whatever she wants. She is the
entrepreneur. You have a lot of work
stuff here. Okay. But this is for love
and relationships. The Queen of Wands is
the most sexual. Yeah, I told you she's
a magnet. So, she remember you got Venus
and so Venus in Gemini. That's very
social. That's magnetism. Even the
Mercury sexile Venus. So, yeah, you're
going to feel that. It's going to be
really nice. And you have the queen of
pentacles who also has a lot of like
elements
that like magician energy. Okay. Um so
there does seem like there is something
here like a new feeling for you but
there's still that I want to take care
of this relationship. I want to be the
person. I want to be the protector. I
want to be the provider but I also want
to have a lot of fun and I want to be
the one that Do you know what I mean?
Like that kind of energy but you're
going to feel that fear like queen. It's
a lead. They're leaders. Yeah, I said
you're going to feel a lot of power. So,
this is really great. Queen of
Pentacles, it's your physical reality.
So, you know, it's like this world that
you envision for yourself that you want
to build for yourself where someone else
is within your vision of your future of
the world that you want to build.
Anyway, I love this. So, things look
good is all I'm saying. Now, let's see
career. And if you're not here for
career, let's call it career, purpose,
or passion.
Okay.
Uh, you
are good. You have the Knight of
Pentacles. You're in it to win it when
it comes to career. And remember, you're
it's all about wealth building. I told
you when you got Uranus and Venus and
Gemini, Venus, a planet of money by the
way. And Gemini uh in your eighth,
that's about building partnerships,
building, you know, even like wealth
building. You have Mercury, Gemini's
ruler in Leo in your 10th house of
career doing things for you. Sure, it's
going retrograde, but you're going
within old bosses, former bosses coming
back, right? Maybe offering you stuff,
colleagues, employees as well. So,
you're set. You're good. Yeah, the
Knight of Pentacles. So, that is wealth
building.
Knight of Pentacles is also Virgo. So,
as long as there there's just going to
be some adjustment for you. Remember
that rules your 11th house of your
future. He's all he's connected to his
future. The Knight of Pentacles.
It's and he's very patient.
Anyway, you're you're actually really
good here. So, put all your energy into
what you want longlasting.
You got to go within though. Anyway,
health. Let's look at health. Scorpio
sun, moon, and rising. You got Yeah.
Wow.
So remember Mars and the south node in
Virgo which rules health. Okay.
You have the seven of swords
and the eight of swords down here.
You got to be honest with yourself about
something. Okay. That's all there is.
Okay. And then to be honest when you've
got Saturn and Neptune and Aries and
Chiron in Aries and your six that rules
health as well. Yeah. Is there something
that you are
holding holding in
that's not good for your health mentally
and it's all connected. mental health
affects your physical health affects
your emotional health affects your
spiritual health. So there's something
here. You got it's like you got to see
something. You got to face something.
All right? And that's going to improve
your overall wellness. All right? So
just keep that in mind. That's the seven
of swords. The other thing is if there
are things that are happening within
your world, right? Someone that may be
cheating on you, lying to you because
this is the card of lying, cheating,
stealing, deception as well. So it might
not even be you. There may be something
that's happening where you're just kind
of turning a blind eye. All right. But
you have all this potential to own this
situation.
So, okay.
You got to have self-belief.
I'll do a clarify for that one.
Yeah, you're going to be fine as long as
you are honest with yourself with
something inside you. You got to say you
got to say it. Remember Mercury sexile
Venus. That's a perfect opportunity. Say
what's on your mind. Nine of Pentacles.
You and all your pentacles. I don't even
know where to put like you. Okay. So,
there you go. Amazing. So, you see when
you free yourself. Yeah. Free your mind.
It's a swords. Swords are the mental
suit for when you free your mind, right?
You got that nine of pentacles
clarifying it. This is not having to
worry or stress and this is earning your
spot in this garden of abundance and
everything happening for you and
freedom. Nine of pentacles is freedom.
Freeing yourself. All right. So, there's
something here. Free yourself from it.
Okay. Now, last card, the biggest
message. What is the uh pay special
attention to card for Scorpio? What
should they pay special attention to
this week?
Yeah. Uh, you got a decision to make.
You got the two of swords. It might have
to do with partnerships and
relationships, legal matters,
everything. You know, this card is
attributed to moon in Libra. I did say
that we do have, you know, the uh Libra
degree activations this week. Yeah. but
also Juno associated with Libra that's
in your sign. So,
there's something here. Okay, there's
something here. And remember in the
writerweight Smith deck, she's
blindfolded, too. So, you've got to
trust your intuition. You've got to
trust your emotions. Again, there just
may be something here you've really got
to look at. or maybe something you saw
but if you turn a blind eye to it that
doesn't solve anything right so
it's being your authentic self that you
want to be I'll clarify the two of
swords and again if you're not here for
it can be care it can be care it can be
career and work you got so much career
work stuff happening and remember also
friendships and you know groups you
belong to societies
your secret society I mean you are a
Scorpio that was a that's actually a
funny joke.
Yeah.
If you listen if all all you got to do
is is be honest with yourself. Don't you
know that's all you got to do. You got
the sun clarifying it. The sun is the
biggest yes in tarot. Have you ever
gotten a tarot reading? Is the biggest
yes. It's optimism. It's opportunities.
It's happiness. It's joy. Vitality. I
said something about a rebirth here.
Well, there you go. There's your
affirmation with the sun with uh you
know there's a it is card 19. Yeah. So
there you go. There's going to be a big
Mars south node conjunction at 19
degrees but also it's a Libra degree. So
peace, harmony, justice, especially with
partnerships, relationships even you got
the moon in Taurus this week but the sun
card 19 1 plus 9 equals 10 1
rebirth. There's something new, but you
got to be able to fade something. It
really is. You even saw remember you got
that page of cups clarifier, that new,
fresh, new energy. What is What is the
thing here that's holding you back? And
again, a lot of it can be up here. It's
a week to free your mind. Anyway, you're
actually really good. I love that. And
remember, this is all potential. It's
the actions that you take. Take that
action. Okay, Scorpio. You are amazing.
I will see you uh next week. Bye-bye.
Hello, Sagittarius. Thank you so much
for being members. Let me move that.
Okay. So, this this week because I was
looking and you know we are between the
full moon and the new moon but with the
south node activation it really does
feel like a type of reset. And so what
I'm going to do is uh you know in the
monthly forecast for the bonus spreads
we look at different themes right so I'm
going to do that because it does feel
like there's some start new start a
refresh or something here that feels
big. All right. So, let's start with
love.
Oh, you got a card popping out for you
already. What can um Sagittarius suspect
with love and relationships? Here you
go. Those two. Okay. First one. Oh,
let's look at them all. Uh yeah, that
may be the thing. Okay. When uh Okay.
You got strength.
Have that confidence. Okay. have that
confidence, infinite possibilities. When
you have that inner courage, that
strength, you can do it. You can get
through this. That's all it's saying.
You've got this. Okay? Have the
conversations you need to have to um
yeah,
should you feel
that you need that, but on the flip
side, hey, a lot of y'all do feel
empowered when it comes to love. Okay?
Again, that's just looking at what's
happening like Yeah. So, love and
relationships looks really good. Just
remember, be your authentic self. That's
a lot of authenticity there in the
strength card. All right. And then the
other cards. Yeah,
you've got to know what you want. You've
got the three of swords,
seven of cups. So, when it comes to love
and relationships, there can be
something that you have to face this
week. Okay. Seven of cups is just really
saying like, what do you want? But you
got to know it. You got to feel it deep
down in your bones when it's like you've
you've really got to know which
direction you want to go at this point.
And even though it's not part of the
south node, it really still is like that
north node activation and Pisces in your
fourth home and family or significant
other. And then you've got Uranus and
Venus, a planet of love and
relationships and your seventh of
partnerships and relationships. So there
there's you're going to have a lot of
activity there. There could be something
that you have to really face, okay, in
terms of and it may just be you saying
like, okay, do I want to change anything
up here? Uranus wants to change what
you've got to change something and it it
be it can be the smallest thing to be
honest, but a Venus is here. It feels a
little bigger. Okay, you have the moon
in Gemini, too. Remember that you're
going to be very It's very stimulating.
It's very social. I feel like that's why
I'm just trying to tell you like have
your moment, but just come back. All
right. Now, uh you I'll do one more.
I'll do I'll
What dropped?
Yeah, it is. There's some relationship
that is holding you back. There is a
relationship to be like really honest
with you that's not it's like you're
that's it that you've got to look at it.
Okay, if you are new to the bonus right
tier three or you know when you get the
same card from two different decks you
really got to pay attention to that
message the five of pentacles there's
something where you feel lit like left
out in the cold someone's not
you're not seeing out of eye with
someone in terms of relationship when it
comes to love and relationships or maybe
you're in a place where you know if you
are single things are not aligning the
way that you want right now again And
this is just a weekly reading. Yeah. So
don't be hard on yourself. All right?
Because at the end of the day, even
though you have Mars in the south node
in Virgo and your 10th to be honest,
remember
Virgo is Mercury ruled shared by Gemini,
which is Mercury ruled. That's
your seventh house where you have Venus
and Uranus, shakeups and breakups
with love.
So, it's up to you. It's up to you.
Okay. Just know you got some great
things to look forward to. Now, uh I
didn't actually those card all of those.
I'll do one more. I'll actually pull a
card because all those just kind of fell
out. Jumped out. Jumpers.
All right.
You've got the Ace of Wands.
to you see all that potential there if
you can. This is in knowing what you
want. There could be the ending of a
relationship. Maybe someone broke up
with you. Maybe you're going through a
process that you know doesn't feel fun
uh in a relationship. Just know that you
got something to look forward to. On the
other side, we got the Ace of Wands.
Something really needs. The universe
offering you this gift that's going to
make you really happy, wish come true.
You're going through change anyway. You
got all the support that's you know what
I mean? like you're good. The Ace of
Wands. Yeah. Okay. Wands are very
invigorating, very enthusiastic. They're
a fire. They're you. They're fire. So,
feel fired up. There's something new.
And it could be a current relationship.
Again, it it's what applies to you. All
right? But if you're single, there could
be something there. If you're in a
relationship, there could be a little
bump in the road. But once you patch
things up, have those conversations,
we're going to be fine. Now, let's get
to career. And if you're not here for
career, let's do career, purpose, or
passion. Let's call it career, purpose,
or passion.
Okay, I'm going to All right. So, uh,
yeah, you're going to be fine with
career.
You're going to be fine with career. I I
really wanted to say like five different
swear words. Like, this is insane. Um,
so again, same cards that pop up. Pay
attention. Career looks really good. You
got the magician twice
again. Something's ending for something
in beginning. Yeah. And you got the nine
of cups
twice. Actually, didn't you get it in
your bonus reading last week, too? You
got the nine of cups twice because you
did get the nine of cups in your spread
last week. So again, do you see how
everything is leading up to something
that you want and you're going to get?
You're good. You're absolutely good.
Now, let's take a look at um you're
having some of the biggest career
changes. Let's look at uh health.
All right. So, um uh great Queen of
Wands.
Uh yeah, she's charming. She's magnetic.
She's social. She's fun. Like people
love her. She loves attention. This is
you. All right. So, be social. Have fun.
Okay. Don't be hard on yourself. Go out
there.
This is great. Okay. For health that
when you're laughing, when you're
joyful, when you're, you know what I
mean? Like that
everything's connected with health,
mental health, social health, emotional
health, everything changes. Okay,
that's why we're here. We're we're all
connected with each other. Connect. This
is a great week to you. This is the last
week I think when you got Venus in
Gemini.
All right, last card. The biggest
message for you Sagittarius, the pay
special attention to card. What should
Sagittarius pay special attention to
this week? Uh that would be the fact
that you are going to have a huge
breakthrough. And if there is anything I
should tell you is to have it. Have the
biggest breakthrough of your life. You
have the ace of swords. You got your
second ace. Yeah. This is having a huge
breakthrough. And this is like being
honest with yourself. True perception.
This is the biggest sword in the deck.
You got a lot of power. All right. Uh it
does seem like uh there may be a
contract like I said signing. There's
something signing. Yeah. Also big
brilliant idea coming out of nowhere.
But you see these paths, these new paths
opening up for you, right? You see that?
So, whatever if this week where it's
just like there's just something like
where you feel a little, it feels a
little quick sandy or even just feeling
like a stop sign like stuck like
literally being the sign on a sidewalk
or whatever. Um,
it's not what you want. It's not what
you want. there's other things you want.
You just got to move in that direction
and just, you know, knights are very
active, right? So, taking that action,
it seems like you are moving toward the
things that are going to bring you a lot
of joy and emotional wealth and and all
of that. Everything that I talked about,
you got the Knight of Cups in your final
outcome, but there is going to be a
little bit of a you're going to have to
make some decisions. You're going to
have to actually look at like look under
the cover for some things, especially
with relationships, career,
family, home. All right, you're actually
really good. Sagittarius, thank you so
much. I will see you uh next week. All
right, thank you. Bye bye. Hello
Capricorn. Thank you so much for being
members. Um we are going to do something
different. All right. Now, what I'm
doing is because this week and
especially for you, um, it just feels
like,
you know, between your full moon and and
the new moon next week, there's just
something here this week, especially
with this Mars South node activation, it
does feel like there's an ending and a
beginning. It does feel like there's
this death and rebirth. It does feel
very significant. So, I'm just going to
do I'm going to pull cards like I do in
the monthly forecast. All right, just
because there feels like some and you
can see there is something brand new for
you anyway. So, let's do it. Let's take
a look at love first. I want to see love
with you and your two of cups, the
magician, and anyway, let's see.
Let's see what Capricorn can expect in
love and relationships.
M.
Oh gosh.
So, uh,
you got the five of swords
and you got the fool.
There's something new happening for
sure, but you got to you got to there's
you got to like let's Can we drop the
swords?
That's all there's to it. Can we drop
the swords?
Okay. And because there's going to be a
lot happening in in your mind, it could
be a lot of tugof-war up here. Remember,
you don't want that energy of, you know,
if you don't drop those forwards swords,
you can eventually get to the eight of
swords. So, uh, drop those swords and
look what happens. You got the fool and
this is taking risks. This is like ready
to This is the you're brand new fool.
You got the fool and the magician.
You're good. Uh, a lot of potential
there. Things look really good,
especially if you're single. Like I
said, if you're single, really great.
Um,
and and that's the case for the entire
year, by the way, until June 2026 with
Jupiter and Cancer, by the way, uh, for
you Capricorn. But yeah, there just
seems even a revival in in some area in
your life. And again, a lot of it has to
do with your mind this week. Now, let's
and spirituality now uh, let's higher
mind. Let's see uh, and physical. Let's
see. Sorry, I keep let's see career.
Let's see career, which is going to be a
big thing. And if you're not here for a
career, if you're not working, let's
call it career, purpose, or passion or
all three.
All right, Capricorn.
Oh, yeah. You, you and your pentacles,
you got the Queen of Pentacles. You're
going to be fine with career. You're
going to be fine with career. Um, it
feels like a lot of things that are
really motivating you and just kind of
like uh where you're feeling that drive.
Remember, you're going to feel a lot of
like that mama bear energy this week,
taking care of others, nurturing others,
uh even nurturing yourself, taking care
of yourself. So, you can nurture and
support others. But that Queen of
Pentacles, not only is she the richest
queen, but she takes care of others. She
has resources to do so. So, she's a very
loving, you know, uh queen, like really
uh even like protective energy and yeah,
she considers others for for why she
does what she does. Okay. So, love it. I
love that. Uh, and again, rich as queen
health. Let's see what's going on for
you, Capricorn, with health.
All right,
you got the emperor. Uh, here's the
thing. The big message coming through is
just really take charge, okay? Really
take charge. Uh, and you'll have no
problem as long as you have that
confidence. And like I said, you've got
Mars conjunct the south node in Virgo
that rules health, right? And your
ninth, which is all about your mindset,
how you're seeing things, self-belief.
Okay? So, have that confidence. Pull
that through. But it just seems like
you're going to be fine anyway. All
right. When it comes to health, physical
health, mental health, emotional health,
as long as you have that confidence and
you're just I is the emperor, that's
literally like a mastery of self. So
yeah, it's it's it's you've got to
believe in you. And in some cases, you
do have to put yourself first in order
for you. He's another person that takes
care of others, okay? He's someone that
would take a bullet for other people.
Like he's the ruler of the land. He's
going to protect his land and his
people. So in terms of health, it looks
really, really, really good. But just
don't like be over, you know, it just
feels like there's so much happening for
you. Try not to overexhaust yourself.
Okay. now uh by taking on a lot of
responsibilities and duties. If there's
anything like just you don't want to you
just avoid any burnout
now.
Okay. So, what is your biggest message?
Sorry, I'm like looking at some other
What's your biggest What is the message
for Capricorn this week? The pay special
attention to card. What should Capricorn
pay special attention to this week?
Yes. So, oh, I'm so glad this happened.
Uh, if you're new, when the same card
comes out from two different decks, it's
over 170 cards. You know the universe is
really trying to tell you something.
Okay?
You can't do that no more.
That's your biggest message. Don't be
hard on yourself. Don't be hard on
yourself.
This is the point where you know there's
something a habit, a pattern, the way
you're thinking, pessimistic thinking.
It's got to go. It's got to go. Okay.
Because just like that eight of swords,
this is also they're they're uh you
know, we they're focusing on their
plight. Yeah. They're focusing. They
don't want people to help them because
they want that uh people to feel sorry
for them, right? And I'm not saying
that's you. I'm saying that's the card.
They're literally outside the church,
but they refuse to look up. Yeah. So,
there's all that. It's a sanctuary, but
they're they prefer to just be like,
"Oh, wo is me." So, no. No. And I'm not
And again, where it falls near stuff,
it's just saying like that's what you
don't want. You don't want any like it's
almost like, you know, there's something
that you have to let go. And this is the
time where it's like, okay, this is kind
of like ripping off the band-aid, but I
have to do it. Like that kind of energy,
especially if it is, you know, someone
that's just not
supportive or, you know, not good energy
for you or anything circumstantial that
makes you feel like you're out in the
cold and alone and you're not supported.
Let's focus on that. Remember, it starts
up here, especially for you. Anyway,
Capricorn, you're actually really good.
Just again, don't be hard on yourself.
All right. Anyway, uh y'all are amazing.
I'll see you next week. Bye-bye.
Hello, Aquarius. Thank you so much for
being members. It is so dark. Um let's
do this. Okay, so what I'm doing this
week is because when I look at this
week, it is one of those weeks that just
sneaks right in. And yeah, Mercury's
going retrograde. We have the Mars South
node conjunction. Those are really big.
Yeah,
but there's a lot of other stuff that's
happening. So, when I looked at this
week, I really did feel like uh I needed
to do more of like a monthly, you know,
like in your bonus spreads for the
monthly forecast where we look over some
themes and we pull some cards. That's
what it really feels like. It really
does. And again, when you've got Mars
conjuncting the south node in Virgo and
your eighth house of death and rebirth,
truly new beginning for you. I mean,
you've you you got the death card in
your final outcome. So anyway, um let's
let's see let's take a look at a couple
things. Let's see what's going on for
you with love and relationships. Let's
start with that. All right. I mean you
you have Venus in the fifth which is
Leo's home by the way and you do have
Mercury which is Gemini's ruler which
Gemini rules your fifth um
in your seventh house of partnerships
and relationships like that's just all
right let's get let's see
all right love and relationships oh you
got the five of swords okay so there is
something here where it truly is there
could be something here. We're going to
have to uh the five of swords is like
listen
it's it's it's a little ego based the
five of swords and it's a little like
it's almost like I know better and I
know how to like it can be like
manipulative energy. They could be like
mental manipulation and it is because
it's like I told you the lower
expressions of Uranus and Gemini. All
right. So I'm just bringing that up
again. It just happens to be in your
fifth house of love and relationships.
Yeah. So there and this is an Aquarius
card. Uranus and Gemini is trining Pluto
in your sign and Pluto can be
empowerment but it can be a little like
extreme too. So there is something here
that's saying like there may be
something that happens to you where you
feel that from a partnership
relationship that I said is going to be
one of the biggest themes for you this
week. Or it could be you. All right.
remember that's a five of swords where
it's just like let's can we drop the
swords? Can we drop the swords? Can we
see eye to eye? Can we talk this
through? All right. And if not, maybe
that's the thing that we have to let go.
You got to trust your intuition on this.
And uh I'm going to clarify that by the
way because I'm feeling something else
for you too.
Uh yeah, there it is. So when so
basically you have the Ace of Wands.
Okay. So like I said, you're moving into
this new when you have a new moon in
your sign next week in your seventh
house of partnerships and relationships.
You got Uranus and Gemini for the next
what seven years. I mean, but you still
have Venus in Gemini for a week. But
anyway, you have the Ace of Wands.
That's new. That's new beginnings, new
opportunities when it comes to anything
that you're passionate about. Wands are
Yeah. That's sexual energy, too. That's
sexuality. That's Yeah. So, you're if
you want that's it's there. All right.
Looks really good. So, the fact that you
have Mars conjunct the south node in
Virgo and of course it's not going to
apply to every Aquarius. You all have
different birth charts, but yeah, the
fact that it is in your eighth house, a
lot of you are going to be ending
relationships, but you see that you got
because something else is waiting on the
other side for you. That looks really
good. Now, um,
let's take a look at career.
And if you're not here for career, let's
call it career, purpose, or passion or
all of the above.
Okay. So, uh, I really need to put Oh my
gosh.
Uh, so, um, if you're new, when you get
the same card that from two different
decks,
it's over 160 cards. It that's you got
to pay attention, okay? Um,
you're really doubling down on that page
of pentacles. I mean, this is saying
this is pretty much like the theme of
the week for you. something new. And
remember what I said, pentacles, your
physical reality. So it could actually
be a relationship, a new relationship
that's rooting up for you. I mean, wow.
Wow. But FYI, remember, we're talking
about career, purpose, or passion. But
relationships, your passion if you're
not here for career like I said or your
purpose, soulmate energy,
just letting you know fifth house is
soulmate.
But anyway, because it is career like
yeah, money, new jobs, new career,
promotion, starting a new thing. You're
good. Health. Let's see what's going on
for you with health.
Aquarius. Oh.
Ah,
I love it. Four of swords. Yeah. So,
remember there's a lot of stimulating
mercurial energy that's happening this
week. And then you have Mars conjunct
the south node in Virgo and your eighth
that is very psychological, very
forensic. It's like there's even like
secrets you want to dig up and things
like that. But no, just have that
stillness that I talked about earlier.
Okay. Four of swords is stillness of
mind. It's like equilibrium of the mind.
It's just it is rest and retreat. It is
like let me realign, work with my
chakras, all of that. But let me just
take that time out.
That's connect. It's all connected.
Mental health, emotional health,
physical health, all it's all it's all
connected. All right. But remember what
I told you it starts this week. It's
really all about the mind.
Okay? It could have to do with
relationships with the fact that you do
have Mercury, the planet of the mind
and your seventh house of partnerships
and relationships.
Okay. And you just got the four of
swords, a card that's attributed to
Libra that rules partnerships,
relationships. You have the three of
swords here, partnerships and
relationships.
And even Mars and the south node in
Virgo, your eighth partnerships. Anyway,
let's see the biggest message for
Aquarius to know.
What is the pay special attention to
card for Aquarius?
That's it
for this week. It would be the uh yeah,
nine of wands. All right. So, uh hang in
there. You're doing a great job. Nine of
Wands, by the way, it's all first. It's
a Sagittarius card. It's actually
attributed moon in Sagittarius. So, it's
all about you and your feelings and
emotions and things that bring you
comfort and peace of mind. Yeah, it's
all about peace of mind about your
future hopes, your future long-term
goals, wishes, dreams. That's what
Sagittarius rules for your 11th. So,
there's something here we're saying
like, hey, there's a lot,
you know, happening this week. Hang in
there. You're going to get to everything
that you want. Remember, you're going
through this huge transformational
process right now. Okay? You you you are
right now and you will be
all year to be honest. All year remember
you have the south end of Virgo all
year. Yeah. But it's really this week
and
the one the solar eclipse in Virgo
that's happening in September that are
really big
and it's good. It's actually really
great when you look at everything when
you do the math for everything else.
Yeah, it's great. So, I'll even clarify
that nine of wands for you. It does feel
like there is something that this week
that you may be going through. You've
got to be very mindful of remember
high priestess and your crown. Yeah. And
then you even got that four of swords.
What I say about the light of your
chakras, even just think mind, body,
spirit, even with that nine of wands,
there is something here that's really
telling you like
connect the third eye like really trust
your intuition because don't forget you
did get that seven of cups in your
future. Um, all right. So, I was going
to clarify that nine of wands.
All right,
hang in there because you're about to
have one of the biggest breakthroughs
ever with that Ace of Swords.
That not bad. That's two aces. Ace of
Wands, Ace of Swords. Wow. Okay. So, pay
special attention to the fact that
you're fine. You're good. Don't give up
on everything that you've worked hard
for, okay? But really connect a lot up
here. Both physical mind and higher
mind. You got the Ace of Swords waiting
for you. The biggest sword in the deck
with that's a lot of power and it is
breakthroughs. It's mental breakthrough.
It's new beginnings, new ways of
thinking. Everything I told you that's
happening, but also contracts.
Something's coming through.
agreements. You're good. Aquarius,
thanks so much. I will see you next
week. All right. Bye-bye.
Hello, Pisces. Thank you so much for
being members. Thank you so much for
being patient with me. I'm trying to
like bang out like, you know, I do 24
videos a week and I'm just like, ah. Um,
that's why this week I'm just going to
do something different and do something
special for you because listen, this
week is one of those weeks, like I said.
It may feel quiet when you know on paper
it looks quiet, but there it's not. It's
not. There's so much happening. Um,
especially for you. I mean, you got the
moon in your sign. You got the moon in
your sign. And then you know when the
moon moves into Gemini that's kind of a
big big thing over the weekend. So what
am I going to do because this week does
feel like you know in between the new
the you know the full moon we had the
new moon that's coming up. I mean that's
your sixth and 12th. There's something
here in terms of like you and uh it's
just something very spiritual something
about you know how you are contributing
to others. Yeah. To the collective with
the work that you do. But there does
feel like some sort of rebirth here.
This new you. All right. So, let's see
what's going on for you. What I'm going
to do is I'm going to pull them, you
know, like I do with a with a monthly,
you know, forecast. I'm just going to
we're going to look at some themes here.
So, the first thing is um love. I'm
going to look at love and relationships
for you. Okay.
All right. So, uh, yeah. So, if you're
new, by the way,
when you get the same card from two
different decks, you really want to pay
attention. The universe is really
telling you something here, right? This
is over 160 cards in in your final
outcome. So, you got the two of wands
twice. Yeah. So what's really
interesting is I kept feeling and it's
right there in front of me that Aries
part of your chart with where Saturn is
conjuncting Neptune. Okay. And you got
Chiron, you have Aries, you have Saras
there. You have so much happening in
that area of your chart. I'm just like
you you've got to there's something here
about you about you with all the North
Node activations happening in your sign
about you. Okay. Uh
and the other thing is and I say that
because two of wands is attributed to
Mars in Aries and so it's actually a
very strong card and money. Yeah, money
is a big thing. You've got Mars, you
know, conjuncting the south node in your
seventh. Sure, partnerships, but it's
still like in Virgo. So with Mercury and
Leo in your six, it's Virgo's home.
There's something here with money and
career anyway. um and finances. But this
is just saying yes,
plan. Don't make big moves this week.
Plan. Okay. You got that new moon next
week.
And it seems like that's what you're
going to do anyway with all these
retrogrades. Now, um
let's look at career. Yeah. And if
you're not here for career, if you're
not here, you know, uh let's just say
career, purpose, and passion. Okay.
career purpose or passion.
Okay.
What is going on?
I don't I don't think this is okay. So,
you got two but what are the chances?
Two of the same. Okay. So, the Queen of
Swords career, there's your fairness.
There's your Right. And again,
everything that's happening here, it
just makes sense. There's something here
like a contract or agreement. There's
something here um where you it you
justice must be served. It must be
served. There's something here that
there's got to be something fair because
you are feeling this confidence, this
self-worth, right? There's something
here that and if you don't get it, it's
like no. And then you have this,
you know, but you're you're you're going
to want it. You're going to be fighting
for it. Okay. Um, and the Queen of
Swords, she's she's tough and she leaves
all her emotions at the door. Yeah.
Because she doesn't want her emotions to
clutter judgment. So, she can see very
clearly. I mean, this is singular
thought here. You even see the sword
pointed straight to the cosmos, straight
to the divine, okay, with with the queen
of swords. Okay, not tilted. It's
straight. So, yeah, again, very
spiritual week for you. Anyway, let's uh
look at uh health.
It does look like health and
relationships for you too by the way.
That may be a big thing. But let's see.
Oh, you got the fool. So, it does look
like when it comes to health,
there is a reset for you. All right. And
I encourage it even when you have Mars
conjuncting the south node. Remember,
Mars is energy and passion and drive and
physicality. So there can be something
here where you're really thinking about
like again it can just be like end of a
phase in a relationship new phase one
that is just so like but even if you're
single or if you're looking or you know
in a relationship all of that it doesn't
really matter when it comes to health
there is just some revival there's this
you know what I said earlier there's
almost like this rebirth you're seeing
something that is going to improve all
of it physical health mental health,
emotional health, but it only starts
when you take that leap of faith, when
you take that risk, when you're ready
for this new journey.
And it seems like you will be.
Okay. But the fool is another card that,
you know, just like the hanged man, it's
like
I'm not bringing the past with me. Okay.
So, it just makes a lot of sense with,
you know, Mars on this south node in
Virgo.
that rules, you know, natively health.
So, the last card, what is the biggest
message for Pisces? Oh, sun, moon, and
rising. Uh, the pay special attention to
card.
Mhm.
All right. So, uh, yeah,
you're you're good. Uh, this and another
card that's been coming out a lot, but
in the second spread, it's just so
interesting. You got the Queen of Wands.
So, the Queen of Wands, uh,
it's very Venus and Gemini energy to be
honest, but also all this Leo energy,
too.
I love it. I love this. Okay, remember
Leo, there's a sense there's like royal
royal maker. There's a sense of fame and
attraction. That magnetic energy that I
said that you're going to feel with
Venus and Gemini, too. a lot of mental
connection here especially with Mercury
right uh in Leo but queen of wands she
is a magnet people gravitate toward her
she gets whatever she wants and so how
because a she knows how the law of
attraction works it's what I say all the
time vibrate at the high frequency
that's you know and then put out there
what you want back but the biggest thing
of all I mean with this being your card
of you know the biggest message,
confidence,
confidence. She radiates.
She that's why people they see her light
and so have that confidence and you're
going to get everything that you want.
And you see that here anyway. And you
know the two queens that you got here
that's I mean you got three queens, four
queens actually with two of the queen of
swords. Wow. Queen of pentacles, queen
of wands, queen of swords. that's very
like Saras Juno
um Saras and Aerys and Aries. I mean
there's just a lot here where it's like
a lot of that divine feminine energy but
leadership ownership. Yeah.
I love this. Have that ownership.
Pisces, y'all are amazing. Thanks so
much. I will and I and and you're going
to get everything you want. You're going
to get everything you want. You're
amazing. All right. All right. Do you
want me I I'm going to do something
here. I I really want to clarify that uh
seven of pentacles.
Welcome to tier three. I mean, and you
know, if you are a member, like I I do
this often, clarify something from But I
do want to see that seven of pentacles
for you.
I have a feeling I know what it is, but
let me um Yeah.
Mhm. Okay. You got the five of cups.
There's uh you're either there's
something there's again something
ending.
It's just you've got to let the past go.
But it seems like if you're the one
that's going to end something or try to
have a conversation about adjusting
something, whether it is love, whether
it is career, whether it's, you know,
with a a friendship, whatever it is, it
does seem like that person may not be
happy with the decision. Okay. Um, and
you know, it could be you too, but I
just don't see you looking back to the
past. I see you ready to move forward.
So again, that's in your external
factors area. Okay, I'll clarify that.
Five of cups, too. I'm very I have I
love y'all, Pisces. I love y'all,
Pisces. All right.
[Music]
What is it? Tell me. Yeah. Okay. There
that there's your affirmation with that
three of uh with that three of swords.
So again, all of this in your external
factors area
there's going to there's and this again
three of swords is a Libra card by the
way. Yeah. So another Libra card and
then the five of cups is you know
actually attributed to Mars in Scorpio
and so you remember Scorpio natively
rules the eighth which is like
partnerships and relationships but
building like there's this depth and
intensity there.
Remember what I just said. You're going
to have all these, you know, the Libra
activations
19 degrees, 7 degrees, but Mars will be
moving into Libra next month in your
eighth house. All right. So, there's so
this is actually good because it just
feels like it's necessary. There's
something here that's necessary. Like
you're ready for something new.
So, just keep that in mind. But it does
feel like it's going to be someone like,
you know, there's going to be something
there where someone could be a little
like, "No,
you are my best employee." You know?
Anyway, all right, Pisces. Y'all are
amazing. I'll see you next He better.